Larger Than Life!
Dead 7 is a comedy, horror, western film directed by Danny Roew.
A ragtag group of gunslingers try to make their way in a post-apocalyptic world.
The twist to this world is that it’s just not barren and
dangerous, it’s also filled with flesh-eating zombies.
The gunslingers will find themselves stranded in a town and forced to make a
choice on either to save the citizens of the town or save themselves.
Jack, played by Nick Carter.
Daisy Jane, played by Carrie Keagan.
Whiskey Joe, played by Joey Fatone.
Johnny Vermillion, played by AJ McLean.
The Vaquero, played by Howie Dorough.
Sirene, played by Lauren Kitt Carter.
Dead 7 (formerly titled Dead West) is a 2016 post-apocalyptic zombie horror western film
written by Nick Carter, directed by Danny Roew and produced by The Asylum.
It aired on SyFy on April 1, 2016 in the United States.
Carter managed to get two of his bandmates, AJ McLean
and Howie Dorough, to star in the film.
In addition, Carter also cast several members from other boy
bands like 98 Degrees, O-Town, *NSYNC and All-4-One.
The theme song "In the End" was released on March 28, performed by Carter,
McLean, Dorough, Fatone, Kirkpatrick, Timmons and Estrada.
The film explores themes of bank, dystopia, hybrid, undead, gang.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and mind_bending.